[
  {
    "front": "réveiller, se lever, se produire",
    "back": "起"
  },
  {
    "front": "verser, diriger, porter",
    "back": "注"
  },
  {
    "front": "pensée, opinion, volonté, attention, sens",
    "back": "意"
  },
  {
    "front": "partir",
    "back": "発"
  },
  {
    "front": "clair, lumineux, évident",
    "back": "明"
  },
  {
    "front": "capital",
    "back": "京"
  },
  {
    "front": "monde, société humaine, ère",
    "back": "世"
  },
  {
    "front": "monde",
    "back": "界"
  },
  {
    "front": "frère ainé",
    "back": "兄"
  },
  {
    "front": "frère cadet",
    "back": "弟"
  }
]
